royalcopenhagen.com 2000-06-10

# SPEEDNAMES

**Privacy Statement for Speednames.com**   
Speednames.com has issued this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: Speednames.com. 

Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. Our policy is in line with the privacy policies guidelines issued by TrustE. 

**Contact information**   
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers).   
The customer's contact information is used to contact them when necessary. Users may opt out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information collected is used to bill the user for registrations and services. 

**What we gather from you**   
Our site uses an order form for clients to request information, registrations and services. We collect users' contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders to our clients. The customers' contact information is used to get in touch with them when necessary. Users may opt out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information collected is used to bill the user for products and services. 

**Affiliates**   
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received from banner ads are collected by our ad company and we do not have access to this information. 

**Security**   
This site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use SSL secure server with digital certificates (https://) and all personal information is fully encrypted during all transactions. Please note that Speednames.com will never ask for any personal information via email. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**   
Our site provides users with the opportunity to opt out of receiving promotional/newsletter from us when we request your information at the time of settng up your "Account" with Speednames.com. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database so as not to receive future communications. 

1\. Visit the Your Account section on our web site at http://www.speednames.com/account.asp.   
2\. Send an email to [unsubscribe@speednames.com](mailto:unsubscribe@speednames.com) containing the word "unsubscribe". 

**Correct/Update**   
This site gives users the option of modifying information previously provided. Visit the Your Account section on our web site at http://www.speednames.com/account.asp and update any information regarding your account. 

**Notification of Changes**   
If at some point in the future, there is a change to our information usage practices that affect your personal information, we will notify you by email of the relevant changes. At the time of this message, you will be able to opt-out of this information usage by sending a message to the following email: [privacy@speednames.com](mailto:privacy@speednames.com). You should also check this posted privacy statement for changes. 

**Contacting the Web Site**   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Web site, please e-mail [privacy@speednames.com](mailto:privacy@speednames.com).
